[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Swedish name of Sweden is Sverige. What does this word literally mean?", "correct_answer": "Kingdom of the Swedes", "incorrect_answers": ["Snow kingdom", "Land of snow", "Northern land"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first TV commercial for cheese was aired in 1968 for which sort of French cheese?", "correct_answer": "Boursin", "incorrect_answers": ["La Vache Qui Rit", "Fromage de Montagne de Savoie", "Roquefort"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mason Dixon Line is a demarcation line surveyed between 1763 and 1767 by Charles Mason and Jeremiah Dixon to determine what?", "correct_answer": "The boundary between Maryland and Pennsylvania", "incorrect_answers": ["The boundary between the confederacy and the union", "The boundary between the slave states and free states", "The boundary between southern colonies and northern colonies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the speed of light in free space?", "correct_answer": "186,282 miles per second (~300,000 km/s)", "incorrect_answers": ["155,342 miles per second (~250,000 km/s)", "124,274 miles per second (~200,000 km/s)", "93,205 miles per second (~100,000 km/s)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two planets of the Solar System, characterized by a low magnetic field, have no moons at all?", "correct_answer": "Mercury and Venus", "incorrect_answers": ["Mercury and Mars", "Venus and Jupiter", "Venus and Mars"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Princess Protection Program, Rosie received a necklace from her mother.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who plays the character of Sue Ellen Crandell on the comedy movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Christina Applegate", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiffani Amber-Thiessen", "Tori Spelling", "Jessica Simpson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the reign of George III, this British politician held the position of Prime Minister from 1783 to 1801, and again from 1804 until his death.", "correct_answer": "Pitt the Younger", "incorrect_answers": ["Pitt the Elder", "Thatcher", "Churchill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous boy band alumni had a role in My Big Fat Greek Wedding?", "correct_answer": "Joey Fatone", "incorrect_answers": ["Nick Carter", "Justin Timberlake", "Nick Lachey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1995 movie Mr. Hollands Opus, Mr. Holland teaches young Gertrude Lang to play the clarinet piece Stranger on the Shore. Who wrote this famous piece?", "correct_answer": "Acker Bilk", "incorrect_answers": ["James Byars", "Donald Byron", "Toots Thielman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A crocodile bite strength is up to how many pounds psi (per square inch)?", "correct_answer": "3000 psi", "incorrect_answers": ["5000 psi", "700 psi", "1500 psi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Dead Sea Scrolls, found in caves at Qumran, are believed to have been made by a group of people called what?", "correct_answer": "Essenes", "incorrect_answers": ["BHais", "Sircurai", "Sarafai"]}]